Guide to the Records of Amnesty International of the USA, Inc.
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series IV: Membership Mobilization, 1971-1995
  - Subseries IV.1: Membership Mobilization and Coordination, 1975-1995
    - Sub-subseries IV.1.5: Susannah Sirkin Files, 1981-1986
      - Annual General Meeting (AGM)
        - Resolutions, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 4)
        - Working Party B--Techniques/Action, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 5)
        - Working Party C--Organization/Democratization, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 6)
        - Working Party D--Finance/Development, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 7)
        - 1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
        - 1984, (3 Folders) (Box 1, Folder 9-11)
          (Binder)
        - 1985 (Box 1, Folder 12)
        - 1985, (2 Folders) (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
        - Resolutions, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 3)
        - Resolutions, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 4)
          (Original)
      - Budget File--Membership Fundraising, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Cambodia Witness
        - 1983 (Box 2, Folder 6)
        - Publicity, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Canadian Section, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - The Colors of Hope, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 9)
        (Short Film--Information Packet)
      - Country Campaigns/Country Files
        - Africa
          - Guinea
            - 1983 (Box 2, Folder 10)
            - Gadiri Camara, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 11)
        - Americas
          - Argentina, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 12)
          - Cuba
            - Cuban Prisoners, 1982-1985 (Box 2, Folder 13)
            - Reports on Cuban Prisoners, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 14)
            - Reports on Cuban Prisoners, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 15)
          - El Salvador, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 16)
          - Guatemala Action, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 1)
          - Haiti
            - 1981-1985, (2 Folders) (Box 3, Folder 2-3)
            - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 4)
        - Asia
          - Afghanistan
            - 1983 April 6-1984 May 20 (Box 3, Folder 5)
            - Correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 3, Folder 6)
          - East Timor Campaign, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 7)
        - Europe
          - Albania
            - 1983 (Box 3, Folder 8)
            - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 9)
          - East Germany (GDR) 1983 (Box 3, Folder 10)
        - Middle East and North Africa--Iran --Baha'is, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - FBI Visits to AIUSA Group Members in Michigan, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Genocide Convention, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 13)
        (United States Senate)
      - Good Group Initiatives, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 14)
        (Essay Contest)
      - Group Assessments, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Group Servicing, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 16)
        (Includes Number Case List of AIUSA Prisoner Cases Closed Prior to 1982)
      - Group Work, 1983-1985 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Membership
        - Growth and Training, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 18)
        - Midwest Region, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 19)
        - Policy/Guidelines, 1977-1986 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Morris, Ivan--Fund, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Policy--Covenants, 1978-1985 (Box 4, Folder 3)
        (Human Rights)
      - Political Killings Slide Show, circa 1982 (Box 4, Folder 4)
        (Script)
      - Puerto Rico Section, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Refugees, 1984-1985, (2 Folders) (Box 4, Folder 6-7)
      - Refugees--AIUSA Refugee Handbook, 1981 September (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Regional Membership Coordinators (RMCs), 1983-1985 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Special Relief Fund
        - Pending
          - 1984 (Box 4, Folder 10)
          - 1984 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Torture
        - The Hooded Men, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 12)
          (Film)
        - Publications, 1983-1985 (Box 4, Folder 13)
        - Standard Minimum Rules for the Treatment of Prisoners, 1977-1983 (Box 4, Folder 14)
          (United Nations)
        - Torture Victim Protection Act of 1986--Briefing Book, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 15)
          (United States)
        - UN Declaration on Torture--AI Comments on, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 16)
          (AI Index: IOR 41/03/85)
      - UN Declarations on Human Rights and on Torture, 1970s (Box 4, Folder 17)
      - Urgent Action Network--Packet, 1980s (Box 4, Folder 18)
      - Western Regional Office (Los Angeles), 1983 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Sub-subseries IV.1.6: Emilie Trautmann Files, 1977-1988
      The Publications Director and editor of Amnesty Action, Trautmann’s records include both subject files and country files. The subject files include files on meetings, issues, monthly letter writing campaigns, material for publications, and Amnesty Action. The country files mainly consist of memos, press releases, and other information distributed by the International Secretariat (IS). There are also materials related to newsletter publication including typesets, edits, and galley proofs.
      - Subject Files, 1977-1988 (Box 256)
        - AIUSA in '84 (Box 256, Folder 1)
        - Africa Regional Conference, 16-17 November 1984 (Box 256, Folder 2)
          (Report on--AI Index ORG 03/05/85)
        - Amnesty Action
          - Action Postcards (Box 256, Folder 3)
          - Board Correspondence, 1984 (Box 256, Folder 4)
          - Budget, 1983-1987 (Box 256, Folder 5)
          - Comments, 1984 (Box 256, Folder 6)
          - General, 1984-1986 (Box 256, Folder 7)
          - Group Exchange, 1984-1986 (Box 256, Folder 8)
          - Mailings, 1984-1985 (Box 256, Folder 9)
          - Printing (Box 256, Folder 10)
          - Questionnaires at Annual General Meeting (AGM), 1985 (Box 256, Folder 11)
        - Annual General Meetings (AGMs), 1985-1987 (Box 256, Folder 12-14)
        - Board of Directors 1985-1986 - includes "New Directions, Old Directors" by Charles P. Henry (Box 256, Folder 15)
        - Committee on Long-Range Organizational Development (CLOD), 1986 (Box 256, Folder 16)
        - Cultural Diversification, 1986 (Box 256, Folder 17)
        - Election, 1986 (Box 256, Folder 18)
          (AIUSA and Board Elections)
        - Good News--General, 1984-1987 (Box 256, Folder 19)
          (includes 25th anniversary materials)
        - Healey, Jack, 1981-1985 (Box 256, Folder 20)
        - Hold For Use (Box 256, Folder f .21)
        - Home Government Work--A.I. conference, 1987 April 13-17 (Box 256, Folder 22)
          (Agenda only)
        - How do I start and end my letter (Box 256, Folder 23)
        - International Executive Committee (IEC)--Sub-Committee on Development, 1986 (Box 256, Folder 24)
        - Islamic Law and Human Rights--Consultation (New York City), 1986 August 15 (Box 256, Folder 25)
        - Kim Dae Jung, 1983-1984 (Box 256, Folder 26)
        - Membership Development, 1987 (Box 256, Folder 27)
        - Monthly Letter Writing Campaign, 1985-1987, (2 Folders) (Box 257, Folder 1-2)
          (lists of government authorities from the International Secretariat)
        - Planning Meetings, 1985-1988, (3 Folders) (Box 257, Folder 3-5)
        - Publications Unit, ,1982-1986 (Box 257, Folder 6)
          (Includes packet from Press Officers meeting December 14-15, 1985)
        - Review and Implementation Meeting (RIM), 1986 (Box 257, Folder 7)
        - Southern Region, 1985 (Box 257, Folder 8)
        - Speakers Guidelines, 1987 (Box 257, Folder 9)
        - SYSTEC, 1985-1987 (Box 257, Folder 10)
        - Timerman, Jacob, 1977-1983 (Box 257, Folder 11)
          (Former prisoner of conscience in Argentina. Includes his address to Annual General Meeting (AGM) on June 14, 1981)
        - Torture--Campaign for the Abolition of Torture (CAT)--Bulletins, circa 1984
          - General (Box 257, Folder 12)
          - #1--Turkey--Info Folder (Box 257, Folder 13)
          - #2--Chile and Syria--Info Folder (Box 257, Folder 14)
          - #3--A Call for Action--Info Folder (Box 257, Folder 15)
          - #4--Afghanistan and Zaire--Info Folder (Box 257, Folder 16)
          - #5--Namibia--Info Folder (Box 257, Folder 17)
          - #13--USSR--Info Folder (Box 257, Folder 18)
        - United States Policy--General, 1985-1987 (Box 257, Folder 19)
          (Includes AIUSA position paper, US Human Rights Policy")
        - Western Regional Conferences, 1986-1987 (Box 259, Folder 1)
      - Country Files, 1982-1987
        - Africa
          - General, 1984-1987 (Box 259, Folder 2)
          - Algeria, 1986-1987 (Box 259, Folder 3)
          - Angola, 1982-1986 (Box 259, Folder 4)
          - Benin, 1984-1987 (Box 259, Folder 5)
          - Burkina Faso, 1985 (Box 259, Folder 6)
          - Burundi, 1984-1987 (Box 259, Folder 7)
          - Cameroon, 1984 (Box 259, Folder 8)
          - Central African Republic, 1983 (Box 259, Folder 9)
          - Chad, 1984-1985 (Box 259, Folder 10)
          - Congo, 1985-1986 (Box 259, Folder 11)
          - Equatorial Guinea, 1987 (Box 259, Folder 12)
          - Ethiopia, 1984-1987 (Box 259, Folder 13)
          - Gabon, 1985 (Box 259, Folder 14)
          - Ghana,1985 (Box 259, Folder 15)
          - Guinea, 1984-1987 (Box 259, Folder 16)
          - Guinea-Bissau, 1986 (Box 259, Folder 17)
          - Kenya, 1984-1987 (Box 259, Folder 18)
          - Liberia, 1984-1986 (Box 259, Folder 19)
          - Malawi, 1983-1984 (Box 259, Folder 20)
          - Mauritania, 1984, 1987 (Box 259, Folder 21)
          - Mozambique, 1984-1985 (Box 259, Folder 22)
          - Namibia, 1983, 1985 (Box 259, Folder 23)
          - Nigeria, 1984-1985 (Box 259, Folder 24)
          - Rwanda, 1984-1986 (Box 259, Folder 25)
          - Seychelles, circa 1985 (Box 259, Folder 26)
          - Sierra Leone, 1985 (Box 259, Folder 27)
          - Somalia, 1986 (Box 259, Folder 28)
          - South Africa, 1983-1987 (Box 259, Folder 29)
          - Sudan, 1984-1986 (Box 259, Folder 30)
          - Swaziland, 1985-1986 (Box 259, Folder 31)
          - Togo, 1985-1986 (Box 259, Folder 32)
          - Tunisia, 1986-1987 (Box 259, Folder 33)
          - Uganda, 1984-1987 (Box 259, Folder 34)
          - Zaire, 1983-1986 (Box 259, Folder 35)
          - Zambia, circa 1985 (Box 259, Folder 36)
          - Zimbabwe, 1984-1986 (Box 259, Folder 37)
        - Americas
          - General, 1984-1987 (Box 259, Folder 38)
          - Argentina, 1984-1987 (Box 259, Folder 39)
          - Bolivia, 1984-1986 (Box 259, Folder 40)
          - Brazil, 1983-1987 (Box 259, Folder 41)
          - Canada, 1984, 1987 (Box 259, Folder 42)
          - Chile, 1984-1987 (Box 259, Folder 43)
          - Columbia, 1983-1987 (Box 259, Folder 44)
          - Cuba, 1984-1986 (Box 259, Folder 45)
          - Ecuador, 1986-1987 (Box 259, Folder 46)
          - El Salvador, 1983-1987 (Box 260, Folder 1)
          - Grenada, 1983-1986 (Box 260, Folder 2)
          - Guatemala, 1983-1987 (Box 260, Folder 3)
          - Guyana, circa 1984 (Box 260, Folder 4)
          - Haiti, 1984-1987 (Box 260, Folder 5)
          - Honduras, 1983-1985 (Box 260, Folder 6)
          - Jamaica, 1984, 1987 (Box 260, Folder 7)
          - Mexico, 1984-1987 (Box 260, Folder 8)
          - Nicaragua, 1983-1987 (Box 260, Folder 9)
          - Panama, 1985 (Box 260, Folder 10)
          - Paraguay, 1982-1986 (Box 260, Folder 11)
          - Peru, 1984-1987 (Box 260, Folder 12)
          - Suriname, 1986 (Box 260, Folder 13)
          - United States, 1983-1987 (Box 260, Folder 14)
          - Uruguay, 1983-1986 (Box 260, Folder 15)
        - Asia
          - General, 1985-1987 (Box 260, Folder 16)
          - Afghanistan, 1983-1985 (Box 260, Folder 17)
          - Bangladesh, 1985-1986 (Box 260, Folder 18)
          - Cambodia, 1986 (Box 260, Folder 19)
          - China, 1983-1987 (Box 260, Folder 20)
          - India, 1983-1987 (Box 260, Folder 21)
          - Indonesia, 1983-1987 (Box 260, Folder 22)
          - Japan, 1983, 1986-1987 (Box 260, Folder 23)
          - Korea, North, 1985 (Box 260, Folder 24)
          - Korea, South, 1983-1987 (Box 260, Folder 25)
          - Laos, 1985-1987 (Box 260, Folder 26)
          - Malaysia, 1984-1986 (Box 260, Folder 27)
          - Nepal, 1985-1986 (Box 260, Folder 28)
          - Pakistan, 1983-1987 (Box 261, Folder 1)
          - Papua New Guinea, 1984-1985 (Box 261, Folder 2)
          - Philippines, 1983-1987 (Box 261, Folder 3)
          - Sri Lanka, 1984 (Box 261, Folder 4)
          - Taiwan, 1984-1987 (Box 261, Folder 5)
          - Thailand, 1984-1986 (Box 261, Folder 6)
          - Vietnam, 1983-1987 (Box 261, Folder 7)
        - Europe
          - General, 1984-1987 (Box 261, Folder 8)
          - Albania, 1984-1987 (Box 261, Folder 9)
          - Bulgaria, 1985-1986 (Box 261, Folder 10)
          - Cyprus, 1985 (Box 261, Folder 11)
          - Czechoslovakia, 1984-1987 (Box 261, Folder 12)
          - Finland, 1986 (Box 261, Folder 13)
          - France, 1985 (Box 261, Folder 14)
          - Germany, East, 1984-1987 (Box 261, Folder 15)
          - Germany, West 1985-1986 (Box 261, Folder 16)
          - Greece, 1985 (Box 261, Folder 17)
          - Hungary, 1986 (Box 261, Folder 18)
          - Ireland, 1985-1986 (Box 261, Folder 19)
          - Ireland, Northern, 1984-1985 (Box 261, Folder 20)
          - Italy, 1984 (Box 261, Folder 21)
          - Poland, 1984-1986 (Box 261, Folder 22)
          - Portugal, 1985 (Box 261, Folder 23)
          - Romania, 1985-1987 (Box 261, Folder 24)
          - Spain, 1983-1985 (Box 261, Folder 25)
          - Sweden, 1985 (Box 261, Folder 26)
          - Turkey, 1983-1987 (Box 261, Folder 27)
          - USSR, 1983-1987 (Box 261, Folder 28)
          - Vatican, 1987 (Box 261, Folder 29)
          - Yugoslavia, 1984-1987 (Box 261, Folder 30)
        - Middle East and North Africa
          - General, 1986-1987 (Box 261, Folder 31)
          - Abu Dhabi, 1984 (Box 261, Folder 32)
            (United Arab Emirates)
          - Egypt, 1984-1986 (Box 261, Folder 33)
          - Iran, 1984-1985 (Box 261, Folder 34)
          - Iraq, 1985-1987 (Box 261, Folder 35)
          - Israel, 1984-1987 (Box 261, Folder 36)
          - Jordan, 1986-1987 (Box 261, Folder 37)
          - Lebanon, 1985-1987 (Box 261, Folder 38)
          - Libya, 1984-1987 (Box 261, Folder 39)
          - Morocco, 1985-1986 (Box 261, Folder 40)
          - Saudi Arabia, circa 1985 (Box 261, Folder 41)
          - Syria, 1983-1987 (Box 261, Folder 42)
          - Yemen, 1985-1987 (Box 261, Folder 43)
    - Sub-subseries IV.1.7: Hans Wahl Files, 1978-1995
      The majority of the files are related to Wahl's work as Training Project Director, Director for Membership Programs, Director of the Action Unit and as chair of the Committee for the Systematic Evaluation of Techniques (SYSTEC). The files are arranged alphabetically under major topics.
      - AI (Box 1)
        - 25th Anniversary Mailing for Local Groups [Packet], 1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
        - 30th Anniversary Packet, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
        - Is this a Case for Amnesty International?, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
          (Decision Flow Chart)
      - AIUSA Statistics for 1991 and 1992 1993 April 8 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Action Calendar Meetings, 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Action Calendar Meeting, 1991 July (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Action Files/Casework, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Action Line
        - Billing Records, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
        - Comms
          (Discussion/Questionnaire On)
          - 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 9)
          - 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 10)
        - General Contract, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 11)
        - Mechanicals, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 12)
          (Fliers, Letterhead)
        - Pre-Written Letter [Script], 1991 (Box 1, Folder 13)
        - Promotion, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 14)
        - Riad Al-Turk 900#, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 15)
        - Script/Materials, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Action on Human Rights Violations Through Human Rights Education Efforts--Addendum, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 1)
        (SYSTEC Techniques Discussion)
      - Action Unit
        - AI Institute on Organizing, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 2)
        - Action Unit Restructuring, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 3)
        - Casework Program, 1987-1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
        - Fellowship Program, 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 5)
        - Freedom Writers Network, 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 6)
        - Growth Figures and Program Descriptions and Campaign Techniques, 1988-1991 (Box 2, Folder 7)
        - Membership Communication, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 8)
        - Membership Department, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 9)
        - Memos, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 10)
        - Planning and Priorities, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 11)
          (Paper)
        - Planning Retreat, 1987 November (Box 2, Folder 12)
        - Urgent Action Network 1987 circa 1991, (2 Folders) (Box 2, Folder 13-14)
        - Unidentified, 1986-1989 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Annual General Meeting (AGM)--Resolutions and Working Parties, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - Annual Review of Country Work (ARCW) (Box 3)
        - 1985-1989, (3 Folders) (Box 3, Folder 1-3)
        - AIUSA Response to the International Executive Committee (IEC), 1990 (Box 3, Folder 4)
        - AIUSA Response to the International Executive Committee (IEC), 1990 (Box 3, Folder 5)
        - Co-Group Submissions, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 6)
        - Responses for the Research Department (RD) and ARCW, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 7)
        - Annual Review of Country Work (ARCW), 1991-1994 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - Benefit Concerts
        - Thouvenel String Quartet--Evanston, Illinois, 1983 March 24 (Box 3, Folder 9)
        - Testimony --Dartmouth College, 1987 October 4 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Board Report--Membership and Casework Programs, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - British Section, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 2)
        (Mostly promotional material)
      - Budget
        - Fiscal Year 1987, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 3)
        - Fiscal Year 1989-1990, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 4)
        - Revised Budget as of August 19, 1990, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 5)
        - Fiscal Year 1991--Miscellaneous, 1990, (3 Folders) (Box 4, Folder 6-8)
        - FYE September 30, 1993
          - Budget Narratives (Requests) by Departments and Programs, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 9)
          - Planning Process, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 10)
        - Personnel, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 1)
          (Budget Narratives for FY 1995)
      - Campus Network Program, 1979-1986, (2 Folders) (Box 5, Folder 2-3)
      - Canadian Section--Manual for Members and Groups, 1978 July (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Caribbean Area Meeting--Trinidad, West Indies, 1984 March 16-19 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - The Casework Manual: A ToolBox, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 6)
        (Created by Group 19)
      - Chile Concert--Students, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 7)
        (Student Trip to Chile in Conjunction with the From Chile…an Embrace of Hope Concert)
      - Committee on Internships and Fellowships, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Communications Unit--Ads/Videos, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Conscientious Objectors, 1990-1993 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Coordination Groups (Co-Groups)-- General, 1978-1986 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence/General, 1990-1992 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Cotton, Stan--Merchandizing, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Coupons Used by AIUSA--Samples of, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Country Coordinators, AIUSA, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 4)
        (List)
      - Daytona Beach, Florida--Spring Rights Concerts, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 5)
        ([Spring Break Activities)
      - Der Cello Clown at Express-Ways Children's Museum (Chicago), 1986 November (Box 6, Folder 6)
        (Dr. Beat Richner)
      - Death Penalty
        - Illinois Coalition Against the Death Penalty, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 7)
          (Includes general material on the death penalty)
        - 1987 Campaign, 1984-1987, (2 Folders) (Box 6, Folder 8-9)
        - 1989 Campaign
          - Attitudes of Oklahomans Against the Death Penalty, 1988 December (Box 6, Folder 10)
          - Campaign Planning Paper and Planning Process, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 11)
          - Circulars (International Secretariat), 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 12)
          - Correspondence Re: British Section's Death Penalty Advertisement Concerning Vermont, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 1)
          - Evaluation Forms, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 2)
          - Midterm Planning, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 3)
          - Principal Actions and Future Plans of the National Office, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 4)
            (Includes Fact Sheets)
          - Swainsboro Georgia Project, 1989 June (Box 7, Folder 5)
          - Video Proposal, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 6)
        - 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Executive Unit Work--General, 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Film and Human Rights--Miscellaneous, 1983-1985 (Box 7, Folder 9)
        (Includes information on Your Neighbor's Son and Candle in Barbed Wire )
      - Film Program
        - Distribution, 1980-1985 (Box 7, Folder 10)
        - Production, 1984 January (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Foundation Proposals, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 12)
        (for Human Rights Now! And Children's Rights Now!)
      - Funds for Freedom: A Money-Making Guide for Groups and Clusters in AIUSA, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Group Assessments Task Force, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - Group Charter Materials, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 15)
        (Includes information on training materials)
      - Group Exchange, 1993-1995 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      - Group Members' Handbook (AIUSA)--Fall 1986, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - Group Profile Instruction Guide, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Guidelines--General, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 2)
        (Advertising Policy and Membership Dues Renewal Information)
      - Health Professionals Network (HPN) and Legal Support Network (LSN), 1986 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Holiday Card Action and Summer Postcard Action, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Home Governments, Intersection Meeting on Approaches to, 1987, (2 Folders) (Box 8, Folder 5-6)
      - Human Rights Now!
        - World Concert Tour
          - Concert Tickets, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 7)
          - General, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 8)
          - Promotion and Schedule, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 9)
        - Campaign, 1988 March 3 - December 10 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Ideas for Prisoners, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 11)
        (Responses to Jack Healey's article "A Think Tank of 400,000")
      - International Development, Committee on (CID), 1988 (Box 8, Folder 12)
      - International Executive Committee (IEC), Annual Reports from Sections to the, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 13)
        (AIUSA Report--AI Index: ORG 40/02/92)
      - International Secretariat (IS), 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - Internship Applications--Summer 1995, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      - Legislative Coordinators Handbook, 1991 January-1992 January (Box 8, Folder 16)
      - Lobbying, circa 1989 (Box 8, Folder 17)
        (Information Packet)
      - Local Area Network (LAN) and List Maintenance, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 18)
      - Local Groups (Box 9)
        - Adoption Groups
          - 1983-1985 (Box 9, Folder 1)
          - General, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 2)
        - General, 1988-1993 (Box 9, Folder 3)
          (Bulk is material on finances and fundraising)
        - Group #113 (Chicago, Illinois), 1983-1986 (Box 9, Folder 4)
        - Local Group Health--Re: Regional Office Interviews, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 5)
        - Local Group Report and Action File Summary, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 6)
        - Local Group Reports
          - Mid-Atlantic, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 7)
          - Midwest, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 8)
          - Northeast, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 9)
          - South, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 10)
          - West, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - Membership--International Membership Meeting and Training of Trainers Workshop, 1986 April, (2 Folders) (Box 9, Folder 12-13)